# MAURICIO ZAMORA MOYA

Phone: +506 83705378

Email: mauzamoramoya@gmail.com

Direction: Desamparados, San José, Costa Rica

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a systems engineer with experience in front end development, using libraries and frameworks such as React JS, Next JS and Vue JS. I am passionate about technology. Organized, creative, honest, proactive, resilient with the ability to adapt to challenges and develop new skills to improve my professional profile.

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SYSTEMS ENGINEERING COSTA RICAN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY | SAN JOSÉ 2018 - 2021

## SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Typescript

React JS

Next JS

Redux

Bootstrap – Tailwind CSS SASS

GraphQL

Node JS

Webpack

GIT - GitHub

SQL Server - MySQL - Oracle SQL

## LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

## LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mauric io-zamora-0279231b5/

https://mauriciozamoram.github.io/ Portfolio/

### WORK EXPERIENCE

DECEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

- Creation of web applications with Intuitive design, strong preference for UX/UI. Easy to use and understand.
- Management of JSON and RESTful services.
- REST and GraphQL integration.
- Development of unit tests using Jest and react-testing-library to check the behavior of the components and functions of the web application.
- Creation of UX/UI components following the best practices and design patterns.
- Use of tools and interface creation processes (Webpack, NPM).
- Design software solutions to meet customer requirements.

#### **INTERNSHIP**

INFOSGROUP OF COSTA RICA AUGUST 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Interact with QA/Test group to deliver high quality software.
- Design intuitive templates with good UX/UI design.
- Implementation of new functionalities.
- Design software solutions to meet project requirements, maintaining and refactoring existing code, writing tests and fixing bugs.
- Perform website maintenance.
- Create readable documentation.
- Assist in the development of responsive, scalable and maintainable web code.
- Work closely with the Scrum Master, Product Owners, and Designers.
- Developed ability to complete delegated tasks on time and work in a collaborative development environment.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

DECEMBER 2021

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1k1MGnTPW5lru4AMwBREySmPB64tAL6Tk/view?usp=sharing

MASTER IN JAVASCRIPT FRAMEWORKS

**JUNE 2022** 

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-9f53dc7e-837a-4eb2-bd73-5950e1ed1a3c.pdf

TEAM WORKFLOW WITH GIT

APRIL 2022

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bHxZY3vm5U-8SfiUPvPnE7ZLGmAFbqa1/view?usp=sharing

AZURE FUNDAMENTALS

**MAY 2022** 

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1YXZvZLoZCzqXI fpD6IJd xtM7a-212x/view?usp=sharing

SCRUM FUNDAMENTALS

JULY 2022

https://www.scrumstudy.com/certification/verify?type=SFC&number=925768